so she
so yesterday I got Omega lizard guys she
was operator
was the nicest and cutest laser operator
I've clothes
I've had ever I took off all my clothes
I'm usually
I'm like naked yeah I'm naked usually
when me
when I'm naked and double bottles of me
they it
they don't touch usually they take it
let's something
let's say they want to put something
over to
over it so so it won't get exposed to
the give
the laser like she did usually they give
me on
me the pieces and they tell me put it on
it puts
it [__] she put it on it for me she puts
it you
it on it and she's like putting it you
know because
know like to put it together and because
in a
in my head I'm like Missy Missy I'm a
guy I
guy I'm gonna get hollowed Missy and I
then I
then it will make it awkward I I guess I
felt gets
felt it you know I may go away it gets
bigger it
bigger I'm like this and then when it
gets don't
gets bigger it's like this okay I don't
give I
give a [__] you know I just awkward I
can't equals
can't control it being touched equals
get is